silverlotto.com 2015-05-30

# Privacy Statement

## **Privacy Statement** **  
From Ken Silver  
**

I want to demonstrate my **total commitment** to your privacy, so I'm going to tell you as much as I can about my full information practices here. I'm going to tell you--in the detail you're used to getting from me-- these things:

  1. What **personally identifiable** information of yours I collect. 
  2. What **third party** personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site. 
  3. More about **us** \--me and these third party people--the people collecting this information. 
  4. How the information is **used.**
  5. How the information may be **shared.**
  6. What **choices are available to you** regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  7. The kind of **security procedures** I put in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information.
  8. How you can correct any **inaccuracies** in the information. 

If you think I'm not sticking by my statements here, let me know by emailing me: [Email me](http://www.askkensilver.com/)

* * *

**Information Collection and Use**

Ken Silver Publishing is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. I collect information from you at several different points on my website But **note this** : I WILL NOT sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those talked about here. 

**VeriPurchase**

VeriPurchase uses information collected from our customers through ClickBank in order to display in the VeriPurchase Customer Widget. This includes first name, first initial of last name, and country. To opt-out go to http://www.veripurchase.com/optout.php

**Order Form detail**

I sometimes request information from you on our order form. Here you often must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for **billing** purposes only and to **fill** customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information may be used to get in touch with you. Generally I will not contact you except **by email.**

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. I do not use cookies to **personally identify you** while you're on our site. If they are used, it's normally to make access easier for you when your return to the website.

Some of our **business partners** may use cookies on my site (for example, advertisers, counters). But I have no access to, or control over these cookies. You need to contact them.

**Log Files**

I may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. But if what you are doing is illegal, then I will use this information to contact you, and tell you what I want you to do.

**Sharing**

I will **not share information** about you with our partners and advertisers. I may use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services, and to the best of our knowledge these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. I'm not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I suggest you be aware when you leave our site and to read the **privacy statements** of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by me. 

**Newsletter**

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, I ask you for minimal contact information such as name and e-mail address. I will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those disclosed in this statement. That pretty much means I won't use it at all. And I'm **very strong** on this part of your information.

**Surveys & Contests**

Sometimes my site may ask for information from you through surveys or contests. You don't have to take part. If you do, and we collect personal information from you, it will only be used to contact participants, the winners and award prizes. Survey information will only be used for improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Referrals**

The "Refer-a-Friend" type of requests are completely optional for you. As they use your own email program, you are not disclosing any more information than you would emailing from your own program. Because of this, you also retain a copy of your email if you have set your program's features to do this.

**Security**

I take every known precaution to protect your information. However, when you send us an email, your information is not protected while it's being transmitted.

When you enter sensitive information such as your credit card number, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

We use a service that uses SSL encryption to protect your security. I also do everything in my power to protect your information off-line too. All of your information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is also restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

**Special Offers**

From time to time I may send subscribed newsletter members special offers by e-mail. This may include information on products, services or special deals. You can opt-out (leave) at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of each e-mail.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if you don't want to receive any further messages from me, I will do my utmost to provide a way to correct, update or remove personal data provided to me. You can also opt-out by clicking on the link at the bottom of each e-mail.

**Notification of Changes**

If I decide to change my privacy policy, I will post those changes here so you are always aware of what information I collect and how it's used. You will always have a choice whether you want me to use your information in this different manner. 

Ken Silver
